早安  名字
Good morning. Name?
等我律师到场再说
Ha! Not until I see my lawyer.
对了  我昨晚还跟他们在一起呢
And by the way, I was with them last night.
麦克斯  这只是春季学期检查而已
Max, it's just for the spring semester.
抱歉  她看太多美剧《破茧威龙》了
Sorry, she watches a lot of Lockup: Raw.
其实我是来还支票的
Uh, actually, I'm here to return checks.
不会有春季学期了
There is no spring semester.
烘焙学校关门了
The pastry school has been closed.
什么
What?
你们可以进教室
Feel free to collect any personal items
把自己的私人物品拿走
you may have left in the workspace.
你去拿大麻  我去拿另一份大麻
You get the weed, I'll get the other weed.
这太夸张了吧
This is insane.
学校怎么能好端端的就关门了
How can school be suddenly closed?
很好  强哥在这  他肯定知道为什么
Oh, good, John's here. He'll know what happened.
你凭什么觉得他会知道
What makes you think he knows?
麦克斯  他就是个大妈型基佬
He's a big queen, Max.
他绝对知道学校为什么关门
He'll know why school's closed,
也会知道为什么女神卡卡上张专辑没火
and why Lady Gaga's last album failed.
尼可拉斯大厨呢
Where's chef Nicolas?
法国
France.
跟他老婆回去了
With his wife.
他怎么会回法国
Why is he in France?
貌似在场的某人
Hmm, turns out someone in this room,
比如我正盯着看的那个人
maybe someone I'm looking at right over there,
跟大厨有婚外情  被他老婆给发现了
had an affair with him and his wife found out all about it.
迪克
Deke!
不是吧  我都不知道尼可拉斯大厨是基
Shocking! I didn't even know chef Nicolas was gay!
别装了
Oh, please.
他如果是基  我早扑上去了
If he was gay, I would've been all over that.
像只大猩猩压法国面包棍
Like a gorilla on a breadstick.
小姐  我们都知道不是迪克
Lady, we all know it wasn't Deke.
是是是  就是我
Okay, yes, yes, fine. It was me.
我爸妈说我骚时  肯定没见过你这狐媚子
And my parents say I'm loose as a goose.
但我跟他不是婚外情
But it was not an affair.
我们就亲热过一次  在六个不同地点
We made out once, in six different places,
八个不同的时刻
on eight different occasions,
然后我就结束了这一切
and then I ended it.
你结束了那段奸情  也结束了这间学校
You ended that, and you ended this!
结束了这一切  再见我的抹刀
All of this! Forget my spatulas!
再见我的搅拌器  全结束了
Forget my whisk! It's over!
《南海天堂》[1947年音乐剧]结束了
Brigadoon is over!
谢谢你全家啊  卡洛琳
Thanks, Caroline!
你干嘛把我说得像是史上
You're acting like I'm the only one
第一个害烘焙学校关门的人
who ever closed a pastry school down.
你去迪克家干嘛非要拉上我
Can't you just go to Deke's without me?
我的心情像跌入垃圾堆
I'm too down in the dumps.
这时候去垃圾箱里待着不是很应景吗
Then what better place to be than in a dumpster?
迪克也说了  一定得带上你
And Deke said to make sure to bring you.
放心  不是让你来搞"三人行"
And relax, it's not a three-way situation.
我们写过三人行对象排行
When we made our three-way list,
你跟泰勒·斯威夫特一起排在最下面
you were at the bottom with Taylor Swift.
至少有泰勒跟我作陪
Well, at least I'm with Taylor.
在三人行排行榜上  谁在我之上
On the three-way list, who's above me?
那个叫薇琪什么的
Vicki what's-her-name
真人秀《桔子镇贵妇的真实生活》里的那个
from Real Housewives of Orange County.
整容很夸张的那个吗
Is that the one with all the face work?
你得描述精确点  她们全是整容货
You're gonna have to be more specific.
欢迎欢迎
Welcome, welcome.
出去时记得擦擦鞋
Wipe your feet on the way out.
迪克  我先警告你
Deke, I'm warning you right now,
我现在没心情派对
I am not in a partying mood.
所有派对都比不上卡洛琳派对
Ain't no party like a Caroline party,
因为卡洛琳派对从不开始
'cause a Caroline party don't start.
我有沉重的负罪感
I'm heavy with guilt,
刚分吃的芝士蛋卷也让我胃部沉重
and that cheese omelet we just split.
我们没有要派对  但我有搞回一包大麻
We're not partying, but I did snatch back the weed,
因为我是完美男人
'cause I's perfect.
很好  我也从厄尔那弄了点
Good. I got it from Earl
据说能让你嗨到昏死过去的大麻
and he says it knocks you out so hard,
他有次用来装假死
he once used it and faked death
好领回他的人寿保险钱
to cash in a life insurance policy.
我干了这样的事  我觉得我们也得来这招了
Well, we might need to do that too after what I did.
迪克  我真的深感抱歉
Deke, I am so sorry about all of this.
我内心充满了悔恨
I am filled with regret
胃里也"充满"了让我悔恨的薯条
and those home fries I just ate.
烘焙学校关门大吉我们都好难过
We all so sad pastry school got all closed.
都不知道怎么办了
We don't know what to do.
我知道怎么做
I know what to do.
吃我包里的奶油蛋糕
Eat the pound cake in my purse.
我们都很爱烘焙学校  对吧
Okay, so we all loved the pastry school, right?
还行吧  不算啥大事
Eh, it was all right. No big deal.
什么没那么爱  我们在
No big deal? We had sex in like
每间教室里与两个楼梯间都做过爱
every classroom and both stairwells.
还在卡洛琳的桌上做过  不算啥大事
And on Caroline's desk, but, eh, no big deal.
算是事好吗
"Eh," kind of a big deal.
是在某个周二  在我的纽约时报上做的吗
Was it a Tuesday, on top of the New York Times?
你们做完还吃了我的蔓越莓棒吗
And did you eat my cranberry Clif Bar after?
我后来可是让某人惨哭了呢
'Cause I made someone cry about that.
是啦  学校是蛮有意思
Okay, yes, it was fun.
但都结束了  这就是人生
But it's over, and that's life.
烘焙学校  没烘焙学校  都不算啥事
Pastry school, no pastry school, eh, no big deal.
-我要把它买下来  -什么
- I'm gonna buy it. - What?
太好了
Yes!
太好了  我他妈爱死那地方了
Yes, I love that frickin' place!
我们一边在你桌上做爱  一边吃了你糖果棒
We had sex on your desk while eating your clif bar.
那里真是太棒了
It was awesome there!
迪克  你是什么意思
Deke, what are you talking about?
我叫我爸妈当做投资  把学校买下来
I'll ask my parents to buy it as an investment.
卡洛琳  你可以管理那学校啊
Caroline, you can run the school.
你现在在办公室里就做得超棒
You're already killing it in the office.
麦克斯跟我可以当校园双霸
And Max and I can be the badass students
完全不屌学校里的傻逼老师
who won't take guff from no damn teachers.
"贱人  你自己去重做奶油煎饼卷
"How 'bout you stuff the cannoli again, bitch?
这学校是老子的"
I own the damn place!"
等等  这有可能性吗
Wait, is this even possible?
这得花几百万吧
I mean, it'll cost millions.
管它的  他有的是钱
Who cares? He's rich!
现在我懂有钱的意义了
Now I get the whole idea of money.
太爽了
It's lovely!
这真是史上最棒的主意了
It's the greatest idea ever!
对啊
I know!
既然我们要一起搞这个计划
And since we're doing it together,
你们两个都得来见我爸妈
you'll both have to come meet my parents.
反正他们也想见我女朋友很久了  麦克斯
Max, they've been asking to meet my girlfriend anyway.
要见你爸妈吗
Meet your parents?
烘焙学校也就那么回事儿而已啦
Eh, the pastry school wasn't all that.
电梯居然直通你家公寓
The elevator opens right in your apartment?
完全与这里格格不入  等等我  鲍伯
Nope, don't belong here. Hold the doors, Bub!
不必了  谢谢你  詹姆士
We're okay. Thank you, James.
麦克斯  你只需要做
Max, just do the opposite
跟你平常相反的事就行了
of everything you would normally do.
已经做了  不然怎么会来
I already am. I'm here!
迪克  你好吗
Deke, hello.
去吧  温暖的拥抱
Go, be warm.
你好  布朗伯格太太  我是麦克斯
Hello, Mrs. Bromberg. I'm Max.
我是管家
I'm the housekeeper.
她是艾瑞丝  在我们家很多年了
This is Iris. Been with us for years.
但你的拥抱很有爱
Well, it was a lovely hug.
我去通知您父母你们到了
I'll tell your parents that you've arrived.
怎么  麦克斯
So, what, Max?
你觉得这里任何一个黑女人
You think any black woman you see here
都可能是我妈吗
could be my mother?
任何一个白人男都可能是我爸呢
Well, any white man I see anywhere could be my father.
咱们走吧  我已经出丑了
Let's go. I already screwed up.
才没有  你也听到她说了  拥抱很有爱
No, you heard Iris. It was a lovely hug.
不过她也是拿薪水的
But then again, she is being paid.
给  还是戴上我的项链吧
Here, better wear my pearls.
才不要
Yeah, right!
我戴你项链  就像猴子穿婴儿服一样
Me in those pearls is like a monkey in baby clothes--
太不和谐了
Just plain wrong.
麦克斯  放轻松嘛
Relax, Max.
你疯啦  这时候碰我
What, are you crazy, touching me?
如果你妈妈现在走进  就会说
Your mother comes in here right now, and she's like,
"就是她  贫民窟的婊子
"Oh, there she is, the hooker from the projects...
跟我宝贝儿子在...
getting it on with our son in the--
高档到爆的书房里厮混"
What, fancy-ass book room?"
你还有知名艺术家的金宝汤罐头画啊
Deke, you have a Warhol soup can?
是啊  以前挂在我房间里
Uh, yeah, it used to be in my bedroom.
后来我用胶带在它上面贴星战的海报后
It got moved out here after I scotch-taped
就被移出来了
a star wars poster over it.
好了  好了
Okay, okay.
你们看  现在我们有共同点了
See, now, here is something we have in common.
我以前也喝过这汤
I used to drink that soup.
我可以聊这个
I can talk about that.
太棒了  好啊
Perfect, yeah.
就聊这个吧
Talk about that.
以前我妈酗酒的时候
Okay, see, when my mother was on a bender,
我都靠砸的来把这罐头打开
I would bust open the can on the kitchen counter
因为我总是找不到开罐器
'cause I could never find the opener
因为她都会拿去用尖端
'cause she'd use the sharp tip of it
去清她的大麻烟管
to clean out her hash pipe.
-妈的快给她戴项链  -妈的快给她戴项链
- Give her the damn pearls. - Give me the damn pearls.
这只是个小帮手
It's just a little help--
帮助你给有钱人们发送
a signal to the rich people
"我也是你们的一份子"信号
that says, "I'm one of you."
就好像重型机车党看到另一个
Like seeing another hells angel wearing a vest
穿着"去死吧  傻逼"的背心  会倍感亲切
with a patch that says, "Suck it, pig."
迪克最好在他亲妈走进来时
Well, Deke better give me a signal
给我个信号
when his actual mom comes in,
因为照现在这样子  奥普拉我也会去抱
because the way I'm going, I'd hug Oprah.
奥普拉不喜欢被抱
Oprah doesn't like to be hugged.
我在她的传奇人物舞会上犯过这错
A mistake I made at her legends ball.
抱了她一下  20分钟后
One hug and 20 minutes later,
我就被换去坐在拉托亞·杰克逊旁边了
my place setting was moved next to La Toya Jackson.
谢谢了  姐妹
Thanks, girl.
你就是麦克斯
You're Max.
我是迪克的妈妈  吉尼特
I'm Deke's mother, Genet.
妈  这是我们的朋友  卡洛琳
Uh, mom, this is our friend, Caroline.
谢谢您邀请我们来
Thank you for inviting us.
您的艺术收藏超棒
Amazing art collection.
谢谢夸奖
Oh, thank you.
我跟我丈夫算得上是流行艺术脑残粉
I'm afraid my husband and I are pop art junkies.
我喝汤哦
I eat soup.
说到我丈夫
Speaking of my husband...
-大卫  -"我喝汤哦"
- David! - "I eat soup"?
他刚才还在我身后呢
He was right behind me.
有时候我真觉得
Oh, sometimes I swear,
我应该在身后留下面包碎的踪迹
I should just leave a trail of bread crumbs.
真好笑
That's funny.
你们稍等我一下
Okay, hold on a second there, folks.
我在发一些生意上的电邮
I'm just sending some business emails.
其实不是啦
Actually, I'm not.
我在看明星卸妆照
I'm looking at celebrities without their makeup,
不得不说啊  休·杰克曼[澳洲知名男星]
and I gotta say, Hugh Jackman?
卸妆比较好看
Better without makeup.
我帮你拿着
I'll take that.
好吧
All right.
你嘴里是什么
And what's in your mouth?
-酸爽糖  -请你给我
- Sour ball. - Give it to me, please.
吉尼特  我是大人了  吃个酸爽糖没事吧
Genet, I'm a grown man. I can have a sour ball.
你叫我监督你不让你吃糖
You asked me to help you stop eating candy.
-就一颗酸爽糖而已嘛  -吐出来
- It's just one sour ball. - Spit it out.
-做不到  -为什么
- I can't. - Why not?
因为其实是迷你巧克力棒
It's a mini 3 musketeers.
他来啦
There he is!
我的乖儿子
There's my son,
但在我们拿回亲子鉴定表之后就不知道了
until we get the results of the paternity test back.
我爱死他了
I love him!
别这样
Ugh, hey, come on.
别在我女朋友前伸舌头
No tongue in front of my girlfriend.
麦克斯  过来抱一个
Max, come over here.
行  但要等吃完甜点后才许伸舌头哦
Fine, but no tongue till after dessert.
"等吃完甜点后才许伸舌头"
"No tongue till after dessert"
她人又漂亮又幽默
She's pretty and funny.
你的保镖是谁呢
Who's your bodyguard?
她是我的朋友
This is my friend...
替我接话  我脑海一片空白
Mm, help me out. Totally blanked.
她有点紧张
Oh, she's a little nervous.
你好  布朗伯格先生  我是卡洛琳
Hello, Mr. Bromberg. I'm Caroline.
用餐前喝一杯  好吗
Drink before dinner, yes?
但一杯就好
Yes, but just one.
绝对不是因为我怀孕了不能喝酒哦
But not because I'm pregnant! What?
坐下  聊聊吧
Sit, let's talk.
是啊  都坐下
Yes, let's sit down,
好好聊一聊
Have a nice conversation,
彼此互相认识一下
get to know each other better.
所以跟我说说烘焙学校的事吧
So, tell me about pastry school.
是啊  跟我们说说烘焙学校
Yes, tell us about pastry school.
我们那天去上学  结果发现学校关门了
Well, we went to class the other day and it was closed,
强哥  一个人很大只的基佬烘焙师  都疯了
And John, this big, gay pastry chef, was freaking out.
麦克斯很会模仿他
Max does a great impression of him.
没有  我才没有呢
No. No, I don't.
麦克斯  你会的  很有趣又很讨喜
Yes, Max, it's really funny and totally charming.
那好吧
Oh, uh, okay.
他大概有196公分吧
Uh, he's like 6'5"--
站  你得站起来
Stand. You gotta stand.
好吧  我站起来
Yeah, okay, okay, okay.
他双手像这样  高高举起来
And he had his arms up in the air like this...
我觉得当时他的手是放下来的
Um, I think his arms were down.
不  他双手绝对是  高举过头
No, they were totally over his head.
她说得对  他的手是放下来的
Yeah, she's right, they were down.
放得特别低  像鳄鱼
Way down, like a crocodile.
或像席洛
Or CeeLo.
你们胡说什么
What are you talking about?
他双手明明举到这里
They were way up here.
举过头顶
Way over his head, and--
对  他双手是放下的
Oh, yea--they were down.
我突然想到他当时是坐着
You know what? I think he was sitting--
而且相当安静
And was really quiet.
不好意思  我想去一下洗手间
Excuse me, I have to use the powder room.
-麦克斯  你要一起吗  -求之不得
- Max, would you come with me? - Try and stop me.
麦克斯  这边
Max, it's over here.
我们不是要逃走吗
We're not making a break for it?
完了  我们是被困住的小白鼠
Trapped. Trapped like rats.
你到底怎么回事
What is wrong with you?
怎么会出这么多汗
Why are you sweating so much?
直接把整条裙子都弄湿还比较好呢
I think we'd be better off just wetting the whole dress.
我知道  肯定是这串项链害的
I know. It must be the pearls.
我这穷逼白人的身体奋起排斥  都累得出汗了
My white trash body is working overtime to reject them.
好啦  把手举起来
Ooh, okay. Raise your arms.
别费劲了  他们已经讨厌我了
Why bother? They already hate me.
麦克斯  他父母才不讨厌你
Max, they do not hate you.
他们会的
Well, they will.
汤米·多伦事件又要重演了
This is Tommy Dolan all over again.
谁是汤米·多伦
Who's Tommy Dolan?
顺便说一句  这锻炼上臂的方式真棒
And FYI, great upper arm workout.
他是我八年级时喜欢的富家子
He's this rich kid I liked in eighth grade.
我所谓的富  是指他们家能买得起祛痘药
And by rich, I mean his family could afford the acne medicine.
他约我出去  但他父母不同意
He asked me out, but his parents said no
因为我是穷人
because I was poor.
事后我怀恨在心  然后用BB枪
And, to be clear, that was before I shot the ten BB's
冲着他家落地窗打了10枪
into their front picture window.
麦克斯  你已经不是八年级的小孩了
Max, you're not in eighth grade.
这是一段成年人的感情
This is a grown-up relationship.
今晚不光是为了烘焙学校
Tonight's not just about a pastry school,
还是为了你和迪克  所以好好表现
it's about you and Deke, so get it together.
这事非同小可  而我脖子抽筋了
You have a lot on the line, and I have a neck cramp.
女士们  我是吉尼特
Ladies, it's Genet.
惨了  要变成人鼠同笼了
Trapped. Trapped like more rats.
里面一切还好吗
Is everything all right in here?
一切都在  我什么都没拿
I didn't take anything.
我...
I--
卡洛琳  我能跟麦克斯单独聊聊吗
Caroline, do you mind if I speak to Max, alone?
我们的邻居来了
Our neighbors have just stopped by.
他们还开了一瓶香槟
They've opened a bottle of champagne.
法国货  超好喝  慢慢享受
It's French, wonderful. Enjoy.
小妞  冷静点
Girl, you need to chill.
你说什么
Um...uh, excuse me?
你完全误解我们了
You have got us all wrong.
你走进我家  看到这么棒的公寓
You walk in here, see this fabulous apartment
还有这么棒的女人  然后
and all of this "fabulosity," and you think--
你就觉得我是那种有钱的贱人
You think I'm some rich bitch.
我的确是
I am.
但我不是生来如此
But I wasn't born that way.
我来自纽约的皇后区
I am from Queens, New York.
没错  我就是现实版的《吉尼特本色》
Yeah, that's right, I'm just Genet from the block.
那你怎么会有钱到
Wait, then how did you get
拥有自己的电梯和鱼图案墙纸
your own elevator and fish wallpaper?
当大卫遇见我时  我还是个跳舞的
Well, when David met me, I was a dancer.
在百老汇里跳吗
Oh, you mean like on Broadway?
在百老汇附近跳
Yeah, well, close to Broadway.
重点是  我们无法自拔地爱上对方
The point is that we fell in love so completely
以至于他第三次来光顾时  我都没收他钱
that I even stopped taking his money after the third visit.
告诉我们  迪克
Tell us, Deke,
为什么偏偏要买一个烘焙学校
why a pastry school of all things?
无所谓  他不混马戏团
Who cares? We're just thrilled
我们就谢天谢地了
he's no longer in the circus.
姑娘们
Girls--
我什么都没拿
I didn't take anything.
迪克还小的时候  艾米和亚当就住在这里了
Amy and Adam have lived in the building since Deke was little.
妈  别跟麦克斯说我"小"
Mom, don't tell Max I'm little.
我好不容易让她相信
I've convinced her I've got
我是她见过最"大"的
the biggest one she'll ever have.
迪克
Oh, Deke!
又坏又黄又好笑
Naughty, dirty, funny.
安迪和我喜欢看性喜剧
Andy and I love naughty comedy.
我们常看比尔·马赫[脱口秀]
We watch Bill Maher.
这个烘焙学校
This pastry school would be
需要投入一大笔钱  大卫
a huge financial commitment, David.
你何不直接去联合广场
Why don't you just go down to Union Square
把一大袋钱烧掉更省事
and light a bag of money on fire?
蔡斯先生  我同意这是一个很大的项目
Mr. Chase, I agree, it's a huge undertaking.
如果你愿意  我们可以讨论一下商业计划
And if you'd like, we can discuss a business plan.
我是沃顿的优秀毕业生
I did graduate top of my class from Wharton.
沃顿商学院  位于费城
Wharton. In Philadelphia.
兄弟之爱城
The city of brotherly love.
我告诉你们  那里很多相爱的"兄弟"
And let me tell you, it certainly is.
我们儿子亨特也是沃顿毕业的
Our son, Hunter, went to Wharton.
他跟你年纪差不多
He's about your age.
我要发短信给他  说碰到他的校友了
I'll text and tell him we've met you.
你贵姓  卡洛琳
What is your last name, Caroline?
钱宁
Channing.
卡洛琳·钱宁
Caroline channing?
你父亲不会是马丁·钱宁
Your father isn't Martin Channing,
那个因为庞氏骗局坐牢的骗子吧
the one in prison for the Ponzi scheme?
这鱼真好吃  我爱吃罗非鱼
Amazing fish! I-I love this tilapia.
这鱼尝起来像鸡肉
It's almost a chicken-y fish.
迪克  你怎么没告诉我们
Deke, you never told us about this.
告诉你们什么  这鱼尝起来像鸡肉吗
What, that the fish was chicken-y?
你们知道这就是我不回家的原因啊
You know that's why I don't come home anymore.
我为什么要告诉你们
Why would I tell you?
偷你们钱的又不是她  是她爸
She didn't steal the money, he did.
迪克说得有道理
Deke does have a point.
不能怪卡洛琳  而且她父亲也入狱了[上菜]
It wasn't Caroline, and her father is serving time.
说到上菜  我面前有九把叉子
Ah, speaking of serving, there are like nine forks here.
我应该先用哪一把
Where do I go next?
你站着说话不腰疼  迪克  你又没亏钱
It's easy for you to say, Deke. You didn't lose money.
我和艾米因为她爸  从顶层公寓
Amy and I had to move from the penthouse
搬到了四层普通公寓
to the fourth floor.
四层啊  迪克
The fourth floor, Deke!
只比看门的高三层
That's three above the doorman.
只有五个卧室  我整晚都能听见
Only five bedrooms, and I can hear the "Whoosh-whoosh"
那个该死的电梯发出的"嗖嗖"声
of the damn elevator all night long!
吉尼特  真不敢相信你居然会
Genet, I cannot believe you would invite
邀请钱宁家的人来你家做客
a Channing into your home.
先生  如果你再说一句她的坏话
Sir, if you say another bad word about her,
我就让你"嗖"的一声从椅子上摔下来
I'm gonna "whoosh-whoosh" you off that chair.
麦克斯  他们是我们的朋友
Max, these are our friends.
卡洛琳也是我的朋友
Yeah, well she is my friend,
她已经过得够苦的了
and she's had it pretty rough.
我不会干坐在这里让他们羞辱她
And I'm not gonna sit here and let them insult her.
你只有五个卧室吗
Oh, you only have five bedrooms?
告诉你  她在墙上睡觉
Well, she sleeps in the wall.
你们有钱人都一个德性
You rich people are all the same.
麦克斯  坐下
Max, take it down.
你晚点会"嗖嗖"地为现在的行为后悔
You're gonna "whoosh" you did later.
不会  迪克  你看这张桌子
No, Deke. I mean, look at this table.
七把叉子十把刀子  有什么用
Seven forks and ten knives, for what?
你知道我们的公寓有多少餐具吗
You know what we have at our apartment?
五双筷子和一个买炸鸡送的叉匙
Five chopsticks and a spork from Kentucky fried chicken,
我们完全够用
and we do fine.
我们不需要坐在这里  鞠躬尽瘁
We don't need to sit here and gravel--
是卑躬屈膝  随便啦
Grovel. Whatever...
求你们的投资  或求他们的同意
For your money or their approval.
我只能说  算你们这些有钱人走运
All I can say is, you rich people are lucky
我的BB枪被警察没收了  走吧  卡洛琳
those cops took my BB gun. Let's go, Caroline.
不  这是我的错  我走
No, this is my fault. I'll go.
不  我们仨都走
No, you know what? We'll all go.
迪肯  坐下
Deacon, sit down.
你不许跟她们一起走
You are not leaving the table with them.
她去哪儿  我就去哪儿
I go where she goes.
除了上厕所
Except not in the bathroom,
因为我们喜欢留点小神秘
because we like to leave a little mystery.
我不理解问题在哪儿
I mean, what is the big deal, anyway?
你们因为她爸而对她有意见
You have a problem with her because of her father,
但迪克妈是脱衣舞女  你们就没意见吗
but no problem with his mom being a stripper?
什么  你以前是脱衣舞女吗
What? You were a stripper?
妈
Mom?
麦克斯
Max!
这事不是大家都知道的吗
Oh, is that not common knowledge?
我好内疚啊
I feel so bad.
不必  我早就该猜到了
Don't. I should have guessed.
我妈打网球的时候身体太柔软了
My mom's way too limber at tennis.
这让我更敬重我爸
And it totally makes me respect my dad more.
犹太人敢娶黑人已经够了不起了
A jew marrying a black woman is impressive.
而他娶的还是黑人脱衣舞女  屌爆了
Marrying a black stripper is awesome.
不是啦  我是为你父母
No, I feel bad about your parents
切断你的经济来源而内疚
cutting you off financially.
但你揭我妈老底  不觉得内疚吗
But you're okay with outing my mom?
他们有让我选  选钱还是你
Look, they gave me a choice, my money or you.
我只花了两小时就决定了  我要你
It only took me two hours to decide, and I picked you.
你要是真考虑了两小时就好了
I wish it took you two hours.
你连想都没想
You didn't even think it over.
直接就跟我们走了
You were out of there immediately.
迪克  没有钱你怎么过呀
Deke, how are you gonna live without money?
我早就住在垃圾箱里了
Hey, I already live in a dumpster.
我习惯过苦日子
I'm used to roughing it.
这垃圾箱谁买的
Who bought the dumpster?
我父母
They did.
顶上的太阳能板谁买的
Who bought the solar panels on the roof?
我父母
They did.
但那个很酷的滑板海报是我买的
But I bought that cool skateboard poster.
迪克
Deke--
好吧  是蜂窝早餐麦片里送的
Okay, it was in a box of honeycomb.
-那个早餐麦片是谁买的  -我父母
- And who bought the honeycomb? - They did.
麦克斯  未来会很好玩
Max, it'll be fun.
拜托  没钱能有多难
Oh, come on. How hard could it be?
我明天起来  就去找份工作
Look, I get up tomorrow, I get a job here,
然后再找一份工作
zippity-boo, get another job there.
很快我就会挣到两万块
Now I got 20,000, then zippity-pow,
然后接着再挣两万块
make another 20,000, zippity-zang.
最后我钱会多得要死好吗
Then I'm lousy with honeycomb.
话说我把厄尔的大麻放哪里了
Now, cheechity-chong, where did I put Earl's weed?
有什么紧急情况  你没事吧
What's the emergency? Are you all right?
我没事  但迪克疯了
I'm fine, but Deke's insane!
他认为他没钱也能过得很好
He thinks he can make it as a poor person.
不要把人看扁  我就做到了
You never know, I did.
当然一开始的...今天是周一吗
Sure, the first-- what's today, Monday?
当然  一开始的一千天很难熬  但
Sure, the first thousand days were hard, but--
迪克根本不像你
Deke is nothing like you!
你适应力强  聪明有创意  会发愤图强
You are resilient and smart and creative and driven.
没人能像你这样  你超级厉害
No one could do what you did. You're amazing.
麦克斯  这是你对我最大的赞赏
Max, that's the nicest thing you've ever said to me.
别这么快就"湿"了
Oh, don't get all wet.
在三人行候选名单里  你还是垫底
You're still at the bottom of the three-way list.
重点是  我不能让迪克放弃他的钱
My point is, I can't let Deke give up his money.
这是他的决定
It's his decision.
而且这是我听过最浪漫的事
And it's the most romantic thing I've ever heard.
是最烂的事吧
It's crap!
我从来没有像现在一样在乎过一个人
I care about Deke more than I have ever cared about anyone,
所以我得把他送回去
so I have to give him back.
我刚打给他妈了
I just called his mother.
凌晨两点  她居然还接你电话
At 2:00 a.M., and she picked up the phone?
对哦  我忘了她以前是脱衣舞女
Oh, right, I forgot. She was a stripper.
很习惯在晚上"接东西"
She's used to picking things up at night.
她说他们同意迪克回家
And she said they'd take Deke back,
但前提是他自己回去
but he has to come to them.
那很好啊
That's great.
所以快点
So, come on.
我们要把他推回家
You and I are pushing him home...
连人带垃圾箱一起送回去
in the dumpster.
把这玩意一路推到上东区
Pushing it to the upper east side?
是的
Yes!
厄尔的大麻让他昏睡过去了
He's totally knocked out on Earl's weed.
他不会有感觉的
He will not feel a thing.
快点过来帮我推
Come on, help me push right now
不然我怕我晚点回后悔
before I realize what I'm losing
然后会改变主意  快
and change my mind. Go!
你推那边  我推这边
You take that side, I'll take this,
不到目的地  决不停下来
And we won't stop till we're there
或推到我们其中一人摔下布鲁克林桥为止
or one of us falls off the Brooklyn bridge.
我们推不了这么远  麦克斯
We can never get it there, Max.
那我们就有多远推多远
Then we'll get it as far as we can,
至少等早上迪克醒来的时候
and then at least when Deke wakes up
他不是在我身边  跟我一起过穷日子
he won't be stuck here with me in the morning,
他可以过回以前的生活
and he can have a life.
我之前说错了
I was wrong earlier.
这才是我见过最浪漫的事情
This is the most romantic thing I've ever seen.
推的时候小心点  不要被划伤
Yeah, don't cut yourself on the dumpster
否则你会得破伤风的  快推
or you'll get lockjaw. Push.
麦克斯
Oh, Max.
这个锻炼上臂的方式更棒
Even better upper arm workout!
只有你才会这么说
Only you would say that!